Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts, 1924-1957 RL.11870
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Contracts for Broadcasting, 1929-1949; undated; 1
  - Standard Brands--Yeast for Bread--Three Bakers Program, 1931-1938; 81
    - Folios, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 144)
    - Forrest Layman, 1937 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Francis Lederer, 1938 May 22 (Film-reel 144)
    - Frank Moulan, 1936 Nov. 22 (Film-reel 144)
    - Fred E. Baer, 1936 Dec. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gail Patrick, 1938 June 26 (Film-reel 144)
    - George Adams, 1937 Apr. 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - George Raft, 1937 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 144)
    - George Stone, 1938 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 144)
    - George V. de Rabin, 1936 Dec. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - George Washington, 1936 Nov. 29 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ginger Rogers, 1937 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gladys George, 1938 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 144)
    - Glenda Farrell, 1937 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gloria Blondell, 1938 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Graham McNamee, 1937 Apr. 5-June 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Grantland and Florence Rice, 1938 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 144)
    - Great Moments in History, 1932-1933 (Film-reel 144)
      William Arts and 16-piece orchestra; Merrill Denison
    - Gus McClellan, 1937 May 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - H. V. Kaltenborn, 1935 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Harry Haberman, 1937 Jan. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Hector Caderette, 1937 Feb. 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Henry M. Druckman, 1937 Mar. 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Henry Scott, 1936 Nov. 22 (Film-reel 144)
    - Howard Hill, 1938 May 29 (Film-reel 144)
    - Hugh Daniel, 1938 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Hugh Herbert, 1938 May 8 (Film-reel 144)
    - Humphrey Bogart, 1938 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - I Love a Man in Uniform--Release, 1932 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ida Lupino, 1938 Feb. 6; Mar. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jack Johnson, 1936 Oct. 18 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jack Mulhall, 1938 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joan Bennett, 1938 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joan Blondell, 1938 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joe Penner, 1933-1935 (Film-reel 144)
    - John Barrymore, 1937 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - John Hupp, 1937 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - John J. Connors, 1937 Feb. 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - John McClain, 1938 June 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - John McCormack, 1938 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - John W. and Catherine Gross, 1936 Dec. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - John Zemla, 1937 Feb. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - John Zemla Jr., 1937 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joseph J. Casey, 1937 Jan. 31 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joseph Spah, 1937 May 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joseph T. Higgins, 1937 Mar. 14 (Film-reel 144)
    - Lela Rogers, 1937 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 144)
    - Leo Carrillo, 1937 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - Leo Reisman, 1931 Jan. 22 (Film-reel 144)
    - Lester Larson, 1937 Jan. 31 (Film-reel 144)
    - Louise Fazenda, 1937 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mack Grey, 1938 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 144)
    - Madeleine Carroll, 1938 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 144)
    - Major C.M. Russell, 1936 Nov. 8 (Film-reel 144)
    - Marek Windheim, 1938 June 26 (Film-reel 144)
    - Margaret Cryan, 1937 June 6 (Film-reel 144)
    - Margo, 1938 May 22 (Film-reel 144)
    - Margy Staton, 1937 June 6 (Film-reel 144)
    - Marjorie Weaver, 1937 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Maureen O'Sullivan, 1938 June 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - Maxie Rosenbloom, 1938 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - May Robson, 1937 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mel Blanc as Porky Pig, 1938 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Men About Town, 1931 Oct. 4-1932 June 26 (Film-reel 144)
      Frank Luther, Jack Parker, Darrell Woodyard, Will Donaldson, Ray Perkins
    - Miriam Cooper, 1937 June 6 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mischa Auer, 1938 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mrs. Alice Dionna, 1936 Nov. 29 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mrs. Casey Jones, 1937 Feb. 14 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mrs. Dewey Joseph, 1937 Mar. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mrs. E.M. Douglas, 1936 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mrs. Edward Arnold, 1938 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mrs. Lizette Kroth, 1937 Apr. 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - Mrs. Miner Crary, 1936 Dec. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Nat Pendleton, 1938 June 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - Norman B. Curtice, 1937 May 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Oliver Cowan, 1937 Apr. 18 (Film-reel 144)
    - Olympe Bradna, 1937 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - Orville Cope Jr., 1937 May 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ozzie Nelson, 1938 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ozzie Nelson and Harriet Hilliard, 1933-1938 (Film-reel 144)
    - Pat O'Brien, 1938 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Paul Charles Santa Klaus, 1936 Dec. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Paul Henry Sadowski, 1937 Jan. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Paul Lewis, 1936 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Paul S. Radman, 1937 Jan. 24 (Film-reel 144)
    - Peg Murray, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 144)
    - Peter Freuchen, 1937 Mar. 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Phyllis Kennedy, 1938 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Popeye--Consent, 1936 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ralph Bellamy, 1937 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Randolph Scott, 1938 June 19 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ray Myers, 1937 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ray Perkins, 1931 Oct. 23; 29 (Film-reel 144)
    - Richard Arlen, 1937 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Richard Lucas, 1937 Mar. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Robert Ripley, 1935 May 4-1937 June 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Robert Stone, 1937 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 144)
    - Robert Wadlow, 1937 Apr. 11 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ruby Keeler, 1937 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Sally Eilers, 1938 June 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - Sgt. Alvin C. York, 1936 Nov. 8 (Film-reel 144)
    - Sylvia Froos, 1932 Apr. 3-June 26 (Film-reel 144)
    - The Carlson Sisters, 1937 Apr. 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - The Zayzo Boys, 1937 Apr. 11 (Film-reel 144)
    - This Hero Business--Consent, 1938 May 29 (Film-reel 144)
    - Thomas Breneman, 1937 Sept. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Thomas Bullock, 1937 June 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Thomas W. Sheridan, 1937 Feb. 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Three Bakers Trio (NBC), 1931 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Tom Hurley, 1937 Jan. 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - Valient is the Word for Carrie--Consent, 1938 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 144)
    - Walt Disney--Agreement, 1937 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Walter Catlett, 1938 May 1 (Film-reel 144)
    - Walter Connolly, 1938 May 29 (Film-reel 144)
    - Wesley Ruggles, 1937 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Will Purvis, 1936 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - William MacInnis, 1937 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 144)
    - Willis Tucker, 1937 Feb. 14 (Film-reel 144)
    - WMAQ: Russell Pratt, Ransom Sherman, Joe Randolph, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 144)
    - Zazu Pitts, 1937 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 144)
  - Standard Brands--Yeast for Health--Rudy Vallee Program, 1935; 82
    - Jerry Belcher, 1935 (Film-reel 146)
    - Parks Johnson, 1935 (Film-reel 146)
  - Standard Brands--Yeast for Health--Three Bakers Program, 1929-1940; 83
    - A Kiss for Cinderella--Consent, 1935 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - A Marriage Has Been Arranged--Consent, 1934 (Film-reel 138)
    - A Morality Play for the Leisure Classes--Consent, 1935 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 144)
    - A Tale of Two Cities--Consent, 1936 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Accent on Youth--Consent, 1935 Jan. 17 (Film-reel 138)
    - Adelaide Klein, 1936 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Adler-Kirkland and others at Group Theatre Acting, 1936 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Aileen Stanley, 1931 Jan. 15; Aug. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Al Altman, 1936 July 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Al Rider Trio, 1936 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Al Seagle and Lillian Miles, 1933 June 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Alan Watrous, 1930 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 138)
    - Alexander Kirkland, 1936 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 144)
    - Alfred Shirley, 1929 Nov. 21; 28 (Film-reel 138)
    - Alice Frost, 1936 June 25; July 23; 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Alla Zimi and Marion Carter, 1932 May 12 (Film-reel 138)
    - Allan Jones, 1937 July 23-Sept. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Allen Cross and Henry Dunn, 1934 May 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Alma Turner, 1937 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 144)
    - Alois Havrilla, 1931 Aug. 6; 1933 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Amanda Randolph, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 144)
    - Amy Goldsmith, 1932 Feb. 25-Mar. 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - Anatol, 1934 Feb. 15 (Film-reel 138)
    - Andres Segovia, 1935 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Andrew Love, 1936 Jan. 9; 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Anne Brown, 1935 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Annie--Zeke--Judy and Pete, 1933 Apr. 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Anthony and Cleopatra--Consent, 1936 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Aristide de Leoni, 1932 June 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Arlene Jackson, 1936 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Armida, 1934 Mar. 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Arthur Allen, 1936 June 4 (Film-reel 144)
    - Awake and Sing--Consent, 1935 Apr. 11 (Film-reel 138)
    - B. Patrick Abbott, 1936 July 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Baby Rose Marie, 1930 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ballad of the Harpweaver, 1934 Jan. 25 (Film-reel 138)
    - Barry and Whittledge, 1933 July 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Beale Street Boys, 1937 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 144)
    - Beatrice Kay, 1936 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - Beatrice Lillie, 1932; 1934 (Film-reel 138)
    - Beatrice Lillie, 1936 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Bebe Daniels, 1932 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 138)
    - Bebe Daniels and Ben Lyon, 1934 Dec. 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Bela Lugosi and Minnie Dupree, 1933 Oct. 12 (Film-reel 138)
    - Belle Baker, 1930 July 3; Nov. 5 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ben Grauer, 1936 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ben Pollack and Orchestra, 1929 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 138)
    - Bernice Claire, 1931 Mar. 26; JULY 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Bert Lahr, 1936 Jan. 16; June 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Bill Bailey, 1937 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 144)
    - Bill Corum, Frank Wotanski, Micky McAvoy, 1936 June 18 (Film-reel 144)
    - Billy Adams, 1937 May 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Billy Halop, 1936 Mar. 5; Apr. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Billy Hayward, Cliff Allen, 1936 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Billy Jones and Ernie Hare, 1933 July 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Blanche Yurka, 1936 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Block and Sally--Otis Skinner and Randall Sisters, 1932 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Blossom Seeley and Benny Fields, 1934 June 7-Sept. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Bob Armstrong, 1934 Aug. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Bob Burns, 1935 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - Bob Hope, 1933 June 8; 1934 Mar. 22 (Film-reel 138)
    - Bob Ripley, 1935 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Bobbie Caston, 1937 May 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Boris Karloff, 1936 Feb. 7; Sept. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Borrah Minevitch, 1931 Oct. 8; 1934 Aug. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Boswell Sisters, 1935 Jan. 24 (Film-reel 138)
    - Box Car--Consent, 1936 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Brad Sutton, 1929 Sept. 19; Oct. 31 (Film-reel 138)
    - Brennan and Rogers, 1933 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Brian Aherne, 1935 Nov. 28; 1936 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 144)
    - Brown Sisters Trio, 1936 Feb. 7; Mar. 19 (Film-reel 144)
    - Brox Sisters, 1930 Nov. 27; 1931 July 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Buck and Bubbles, 1934 Feb. 15; 1935 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 138)
      African American vaudeville duo of tap dancer John William Sublett (1902-1986, stage name John W. Bubbles) and pianist Ford Lee "Buck" Washington (1903-1955)
    - Buddy Rogers, 1937 July 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Burford Hampden, 1936 June 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Cab Calloway, 1933 Sept. 21; 1934 May 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - Call It a Day--Consent, 1936 May 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Calypso Bond, 1934 Mar. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Captain Blood--Consent, 1935 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Captain Kidd--Consent, 1936 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - Carl Hubbell, 1936 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Carmel Myers, 1933 Oct. 19 (Film-reel 138)
    - Carolin Trio, 1930 June 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Carrie Jacobs Band, 1935 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Cavaliers Quartet, 1929 Oct. 17; 1934 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Cecil Lean and Mayfield, 1933 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Celia Villa, 1934 Aug. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Charles Alcott, 1934 June 28 (Film-reel 138)
    - Charles Butterworth, 1936 Aug. 13; 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Charles Sale and Jeanne Amber, 1934 Aug. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Charles Singer, 1936 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Charles Timblin, 1934 Sept. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Chase Baremco, Willie and Eugenie Howard, 1932 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Chick Sales, 1929 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Claire Madjette, 1931 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - Claudia Morgan, 1936 June 4 (Film-reel 144)
    - Clear All Wires--Consent, 1935 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - Cleo Brown, 1937 May 7 (Film-reel 144)
      Stage name of Cleopatra Brown, jazz and blues musician, first female recipient of the NEW Jazz Masters Fellowship
    - Cliff Lowe, 1936 July 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Clyde Fillmore, 1936 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Colin Clive, 1935 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 144)
    - Collins and Peterson, 1933 Nov. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Conrad Nagel, 1935 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 144)
    - Corinna Mura, 1935 Mar. 14 (Film-reel 138)
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1931 May 14; 1934 Aug. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1936 Apr. 30; June 18 (Film-reel 144)
    - Countess Olga Medolago Albani, 1929 Dec. 19; 1930 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Created--Consent, 1936 May 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Cross and Dunn, 1934 Apr. 19 (Film-reel 138)
    - Cross and Dunn, 1936 June 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Curt Peterson, 1931 May 7; 14 (Film-reel 138)
    - Cyril Smith, 1935 Dec. 12; 1936 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Dave Apollon, 1933 Sept. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Dave Oliver, 1936 May 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - David Bethea, 1936 July 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - David Freedman, 1935 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - David Guion, 1936 July 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - De Wolf Hopper, 1933 May 18 (Film-reel 138)
    - Derby Wilson, 1937 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Dick Grace, 1935 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - Dick Powell, 1937 July 18; Sept. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Dick Shelton, 1935 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Do Re Mi Trio, 1934 June 14-28 (Film-reel 138)
    - Do You Minn It--Consent, 1936 July 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Doc Rockwell, 1936 July 9-Sept. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Don Cossacks, 1935 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Don Johnson, 1936 May 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Donald H. Johnson, 1936 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Doris Wesler, 1935 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Dorothy Dell, 1932 Apr. 14 (Film-reel 138)
    - Dorothy Stone, 1934 Aug. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Dorothy Thompson, 1936 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 144)
    - Douglas Fairbanks Jr., 1936 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Dr. James R. Houghton, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 144)
    - Dr. William L. Stidger, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 144)
    - Duncan Sisters, 1935 Apr. 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Earl Hines and Catherine Perry, 1935 Mar. 21 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ed East and Ralph Dumke, 1933 May 25 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ed Green and Company, 1934 Jan. 18 (Film-reel 138)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1931 Feb. 5; Oct. 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1936 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Eddie Dowling, 1935 Feb. 21 (Film-reel 138)
    - Eddie Dowling, Ray Dooley, 1936 July 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Eddie Garr, 1934 Jan. 25 (Film-reel 138)
    - Eddie Garr, 1935 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Eddie Green, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 144)
    - Eddie Leonard, 1934 Mar. 15 (Film-reel 138)
    - Eddie Peabody, 1931 May 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Eddie Peabody and Peggy Healy, 1932 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Eddie Stanley, 1935 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Edith Evans and Ray Mayer, 1933 July 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Edna Barr, 1936 July 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Edward F. MacCauley, 1936 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Edward G. Robinson, 1935 Oct. 10; 1936 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Edward Goodman, 1936 June 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Edward Thorgerson, 1929 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - Edyth Wilson, 1937 May 28-June 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Efrem Zembalist, 1936 May 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Eileen Barton, 1936 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 144)
    - El Brendel, 1934 Feb. 22 (Film-reel 138)
    - El Brendel, 1936 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ella Logan, 1935 Apr. 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Emil Boreo, 1936 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ernest Whitman, 1936 Apr. 9; 16 (Film-reel 144)
    - Errol Flynn, 1935 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ethan Frome--Consent, 1936 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ethel Barrymore, 1935 Feb. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ethel Browning, 1936 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ethel Levery, 1934 Apr. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ethel Merman, 1932 Dec. 18 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ethel Waters, 1931 Aug. 13; 1933 May 11 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ethel Waters, 1937 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Eugene List, 1936 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Eva La Gallienne and Rudolph Schildkrauer Jr., 1932 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Evelyn Laye, 1934 Feb. 22 (Film-reel 138)
    - Fanny Brice, 1930-1934 (Film-reel 138)
    - Fanny Brice, 1936 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Fanny MacBaldridge, 1936 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Felix Salmond, 1933 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Fields & McHugh, 1932 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 138)
    - Five Cabin Kids, 1934 July 19 (Film-reel 138)
    - Florence Malone, 1929 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 138)
    - Florence Malone, 1936 Apr. 9; June 4 (Film-reel 144)
    - Flying Colors--Consent, 1936 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Folios, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 144)
    - Four Musicians, 1930 Dec. 18 (Film-reel 138)
    - Foursome Quartet, 1932 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Frances Langford, 1931 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 138)
    - Frances Maddux, 1930 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Frances Shelley, 1929 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 138)
    - Frances Williams, 1930-1932 (Film-reel 138)
    - Francesca Bruning, 1936 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Franchot Tone, 1935 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Frank Bacy, 1936 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Frank Black's Saxophone Sextette, 1932 Jan. 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - Frank Caby, 1936 Aug. 6 (Film-reel 144)
    - Frank Carter, 1937 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Frank Fay, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 144)
    - Frank Luther and Zora Lagman, 1933 Nov. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Frank Wilson, 1936 July 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Frazier Hunt, 1936 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Fred and Adele Astaire, 1931 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Fred Hildebrant and Doug Leavitt, 1933 June 22 (Film-reel 138)
    - Freddie Bartholomew, 1936 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - Freddie Lightner, 1936 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gay Nineties Quartet, 1936 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gee Gee James, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gene Austin, 1929 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 138)
    - Gene Leonard, 1936 June 25; July 23; 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gene Sarazan, 1935 Apr. 11 (Film-reel 138)
    - George Beatty, 1933 Sept. 7; 1934 Jan. 25 (Film-reel 138)
    - George Beatty, 1935 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - George Devey Washington, 1933 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - George Givot, 1936 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - George Jessel, 1931 Apr. 2; 1934 May 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - George Jessel, 1936 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - George Murphy, 1937 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 144)
    - George Vivian, 1936 June 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gerard Debasts, 1935 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - Gilda Gray and Lou Alter, 1933 July 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ginger Rogers, 1931 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Gladys Rice, 1929 Nov. 7-1930 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Gladys Swarthout, 1933 Oct. 5 (Film-reel 138)
    - Glenn Darwin, 1939 Apr. 6; May 19 (Film-reel 144)
    - God Save the King--Consent, 1935 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Grace Hayes, 1929 Sept. 12; 1934 Mar. 22 (Film-reel 138)
    - Grace Matthews, 1936 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - Grace Moore, 1934 Sept. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Graham McNamee, 1929-1932 (Film-reel 138)
    - Graham McNamee, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 144)
    - Green and Campbell, 1934 June 14 (Film-reel 138)
    - Gregory Ratoff, 1936 July 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Greta Keller, 1932 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Gus Van, 1934 Mar. 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Guy Maier and Lee Pattison, 1934 Mar. 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - H. Warden Wilson, 1933 June 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Hallie Stiles, Sam Herman and Green Brothers, 1932 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - Harold Bauer, 1936 July 17 (Film-reel 144)
    - Harold Van Dusen, 1933 Aug. 24 (Film-reel 138)
    - Harry Donoghy and Charles Harrison, 1934 May 17 (Film-reel 138)
    - Harry Ellerbe, 1936 May 14 (Film-reel 144)
    - Harry Irvine, 1936 June 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Harry Neville, 1929 Nov. 14; 28 (Film-reel 138)
    - Harry Richman, 1931 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 138)
    - Harry Welsh, 1934 Sept. 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Hedda Hopper, 1936 May 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - Helen Barr, 1931 Jan. 22 (Film-reel 138)
    - Helen Broderick, 1934 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Helen Brown, 1936 Aug. 6 (Film-reel 144)
    - Helen Claire, 1936 May 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Helen Howe, 1935 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 144)
    - Helen Jepson, 1936 July 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Helen Kane, 1934 June 21 (Film-reel 138)
    - Helen Keller and secretary, 1936 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Helen Lynd, 1936 Mar. 5; Apr. 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Helen Morgan, 1931 Nov. 26; 1934 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Helen Vinson, Fred Perry, 1936 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 144)
    - Hendrick William Van Loon, 1934 May 31 (Film-reel 138)
    - Hene Damur, 1936 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Henriette Schumann, 1935 Mar. 28 (Film-reel 138)
    - Henry Hull, 1936 June 11 (Film-reel 144)
    - Herbert Kingsley, Evelyn Case, 1935 Nov. 14; 1936 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 144)
    - Heywood Broun, 1933 Nov. 2; 1934 Nov. 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Hildegarde, 1936 July 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Hildegarde Halliday, 1936 May 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Hizi Koyke and Maurice Barrett, 1934 Aug. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Horace Braham, 1936 Feb. 20; Aug. 6 (Film-reel 144)
    - Howard Marsh, 1933 Apr. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Howard Petrie, 1935 Mar. 7-28 (Film-reel 138)
    - Howard University Glee Club, 1936 May 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Hugh O'Connell, 1936 May 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - Husbands and Wives--Consents, 1936 July 5-Sept. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - I Live My Life--Consent, 1935 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 144)
    - I Love a Mystery--Folios, 1939 Jan.-1940 May 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Igor Goren, 1934 May 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ilka Chase, 1934 Sept. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ilka Chase, 1936 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ilossy Bailey and Lee Sims, 1933 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Imogene Coca, 1936 May 21 (Film-reel 144)
    - International Trio (Berks Country Boys), 1935 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 144)
    - Ipana Troubadors, 1929 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 138)
    - Irene Bordoni, 1930-1932 (Film-reel 138)
    - Irene Franklin, 1933 May 18 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jack McLallen, 1933 Sept. 28; Nov. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - James Hilton, 1935 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 144)
    - James Kirkwood, 1933 June 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - James T. Mahoney, 1930 Oct. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - James Wallington, 1931-1934 (Film-reel 138)
    - James Wallington, 1934 Jan. 18-1935 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jane Frohman, 1932 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jane Mallet, 1936 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 144)
    - Janz and Whelan, 1933 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jean Arthur, 1935 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jean Hersholt, 1936 May 7 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jeanne Dante, 1936 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jeannette MacDonald, 1930 Dec. 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jeff Machamer, 1936 June 25 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jerry Macy, 1936 July 23 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jesse Block, Eve Sudly, 1936 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 144)
    - Jessica Dragonette, 1929 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jimmy Kemper, 1935 Mar. 21 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jimmy Savo, John Hamilton, 1936 July 30 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joe Cook, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joe Di Maggio, 1936 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 144)
    - Joe Fisco, 1934 Mar. 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - John Alden--Consent, 1936 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 144)
    - John Boles, 1936 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 144)
    - John Griggs, 1936 May 7 (Film-reel 144)